https://regton.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Log In
Cart:
0 item(s) - £0.00
You have no items in your shopping cart.
0
** SPECIAL OFFERS **XP Black Friday - Special DealsNEW ARRIVALSSALEGift Ideas From RegtonMetal DetectorsC.Scope Metal DetectorsGarrett Metal DetectorsLaser Metal DetectorsScanmaster Metal DetectorsNokta | Makro Metal DetectorsViking Metal DetectorsWhites Metal DetectorsXP Metal DetectorsGold Metal DetectorsChildren's Metal DetectorsBeach Metal DetectingSecond Hand Metal DetectorsMetal Detecting AccessoriesC.Scope Metal Detecting AccessoriesGarrett Metal Detecting AccessoriesGarrett Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsGarrett General AccessoriesTesoro/Laser AccessoriesViking Metal Detecting AccessoriesWhite's Metal Detecting AccessoriesWhite's Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsWhite's General AccessoriesXP Metal Detecting AccessoriesXP Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsXP General AccessoriesXP DEUS AccessoriesMakro Metal Detecting AccessoriesMAS Coils for Metal DetectorsNokta Metal Detecting AccessoriesMinelab Metal Detecting AccessoriesMinelab Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsMinelab General AccessoriesMaz Metal Detecting AccessoriesPinpoint ProbesBarrelling and CleaningBatteries and ChargersCarry Bags for metal detectorsClothingFinds and Coin StorageGold PanningHeadphones for Metal DetectorsMagnets for Metal DetectingMagnifiersMiscellaneousFinds Pouches and ApronsTrowels and ScoopsDetectorPro Metal DetectingNEL Coils for Metal DetectorsNEL Coils for Garrett metal detectorsNEL Coils for Laser/Tesoro metal detectorsNEL Coils for Makro Metal DetectorsNEL Coils for Minelab metal detectorsNEL Coils for Whites metal detectorsNEL Coils for XP metal detectorsNEL Coils for Teknetics/Fisher/Discovery metal detectorsNEL COIL COVERSMetal Detecting Books & MapsArcheology BooksBadges and Buttons BooksBeach and Underwater Metal Detecting BooksBuckles BooksCleaning and Restoration BooksCeltic and Roman booksCoin and Token BooksCutlery BooksDress Accessory BooksFarming and Tools BooksGeneral Metal Detecting BooksGold Panning and Prospecting BooksHorse Furniture BooksIdentifying your finds BooksIron and Bronze Age BooksMapsMetal Detecting DVDsMedieval BooksPottery and BottlesResearch BooksSaxon and Viking BooksSealsShoebox LibrarySpecific Detector GuidesThimbles BooksWeights BooksGift Vouchers
Categories
** SPECIAL OFFERS **XP Black Friday - Special DealsNEW ARRIVALSSALEGift Ideas From RegtonMetal DetectorsC.Scope Metal DetectorsGarrett Metal DetectorsLaser Metal DetectorsScanmaster Metal DetectorsNokta | Makro Metal DetectorsViking Metal DetectorsWhites Metal DetectorsXP Metal DetectorsGold Metal DetectorsChildren's Metal DetectorsBeach Metal DetectingSecond Hand Metal DetectorsMetal Detecting AccessoriesC.Scope Metal Detecting AccessoriesGarrett Metal Detecting AccessoriesGarrett Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsGarrett General AccessoriesTesoro/Laser AccessoriesViking Metal Detecting AccessoriesWhite's Metal Detecting AccessoriesWhite's Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsWhite's General AccessoriesXP Metal Detecting AccessoriesXP Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsXP General AccessoriesXP DEUS AccessoriesMakro Metal Detecting AccessoriesMAS Coils for Metal DetectorsNokta Metal Detecting AccessoriesMinelab Metal Detecting AccessoriesMinelab Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsMinelab General AccessoriesMaz Metal Detecting AccessoriesPinpoint ProbesBarrelling and CleaningBatteries and ChargersCarry Bags for metal detectorsClothingFinds and Coin StorageGold PanningHeadphones for Metal DetectorsMagnets for Metal DetectingMagnifiersMiscellaneousFinds Pouches and ApronsTrowels and ScoopsDetectorPro Metal DetectingNEL Coils for Metal DetectorsNEL Coils for Garrett metal detectorsNEL Coils for Laser/Tesoro metal detectorsNEL Coils for Makro Metal DetectorsNEL Coils for Minelab metal detectorsNEL Coils for Whites metal detectorsNEL Coils for XP metal detectorsNEL Coils for Teknetics/Fisher/Discovery metal detectorsNEL COIL COVERSMetal Detecting Books & MapsArcheology BooksBadges and Buttons BooksBeach and Underwater Metal Detecting BooksBuckles BooksCleaning and Restoration BooksCeltic and Roman booksCoin and Token BooksCutlery BooksDress Accessory BooksFarming and Tools BooksGeneral Metal Detecting BooksGold Panning and Prospecting BooksHorse Furniture BooksIdentifying your finds BooksIron and Bronze Age BooksMapsMetal Detecting DVDsMedieval BooksPottery and BottlesResearch BooksSaxon and Viking BooksSealsShoebox LibrarySpecific Detector GuidesThimbles BooksWeights BooksGift Vouchers
Home
>
Privacy Policy
You did not add any gift products to the cart. Check your available gifts!
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how Regton LTD Metal Detectors uses and protects any information that you give Regton LTD Metal Detectors when you use this website. Regton LTD Metal Detectors is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Regton LTD Metal Detectors may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.
What we collect
We may collect the following information:
name
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
For the exhaustive list of cookies, we collect see the List of cookies we collect section.
What we do with the information we gather
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. To prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyse web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes, and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:
whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by writing to or emailing us at sales@regton.com
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you , please write to 82 Cliveland Street
B19 3SN
Birmingham.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
List of cookies we collect
Google Analytics sets first party cookies via a piece of JavaScript code which must be added to every page that site owners want to track. It sets four cookies automatically, and a fifth via opt-in (this relates to sharing information about your traffic with Google).
Globally and in the European Union member states Google sets the following cookies:
__utma Cookie A persistent cookie - remains on a computer, unless it expires or the cookie cache is cleared. It tracks visitors. Metrics associated with the Google __utma cookie include a first visit (unique visit), last visit (returning visit). This also includes Days and Visits to purchase calculations which afford eCommerce websites with data intelligence around purchasing sales funnels.
__utmb Cookie & __utmc Cookie These cookies work in tandem to calculate visit length. Google __utmb cookie demarks the exact arrival time; then Google __utmc registers the precise exit time of the user.
Because __utmb counts entrance visits, it is a session cookie and expires at the end of the session, e.g. when the user leaves the page. A timestamp of 30 minutes must pass before Google cookie __utmc expires. Given__utmc cannot tell if a browser or website session ends. Therefore, if no new page view is recorded in 30 minutes, the cookie is expired.
This is a standard 'grace period' in web analytics. Omniture and WebTrends, among many others, follow the same procedure.
__utmz Cookie Cookie __utmz monitors the HTTP Referrer and notes where a visitor arrived from, with the referrer siloed into type (Search engine (organic or CPC), direct, social and unaccounted). From the HTTP Referrer, the   __utmz Cookie also registers, what keyword generated the visit plus geolocation data.
This cookie lasts six months. In tracking terms, this Cookie is perhaps the most important as it will tell you about your traffic and help with conversion information such as what source/medium/keyword to attribute for a Goal Conversion.
__utmv Cookie Google __utmv Cookie lasts "forever". It is a persistent cookie. It is used for segmentation, data experimentation and the __utmv works hand in hand with the   __utmz cookie to improve cookie targeting capabilities.
The table below lists the cookies we collect and what information they store.
COOKIE nameCOOKIE Description
CART
The association with your shopping cart.
CATEGORY_INFO
Stores the category info on the page, that allows displaying pages more quickly.
COMPARE
The items that you have in the Compare Products list.
CURRENCY
Your preferred currency
CUSTOMER
An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.
CUSTOMER_AUTH
An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.
CUSTOMER_INFO
An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS
Stores the Customer Segment ID
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE
A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.
FRONTEND
You session ID on the server.
GUEST-VIEW
Allows guests to edit their orders.
LAST_CATEGORY
The last category you visited.
LAST_PRODUCT
The most recent product you have viewed.
NEWMESSAGE
Indicates whether a new message has been received.
NO_CACHE
Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART
A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.
POLL
The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.
POLLN
Information on what polls you have voted on.
RECENTLYCOMPARED
The items that you have recently compared.
STF
Information on products you have emailed to friends.
STORE
The store view or language you have selected.
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE
Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS
The products that you have recently viewed.
WISHLIST
An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.
WISHLIST_CNT
The number of items in your Wishlist.
Registered Company Name
REGTON LIMITED
Registered Company Number
1595972
Registered Office Address
82 Cliveland StreetB19 3SNBirminghamUnited Kingdom
Follow us on Facebook
Follow us on Instagram
Follow us on Linkedin
Follow us on Pinterest
Follow us on Twitter
Follow us on YouTube
Categories
** SPECIAL OFFERS **XP Black Friday - Special DealsNEW ARRIVALSSALEGift Ideas From RegtonMetal DetectorsC.Scope Metal DetectorsGarrett Metal DetectorsLaser Metal DetectorsScanmaster Metal DetectorsNokta | Makro Metal DetectorsViking Metal DetectorsWhites Metal DetectorsXP Metal DetectorsGold Metal DetectorsChildren's Metal DetectorsBeach Metal DetectingSecond Hand Metal DetectorsMetal Detecting AccessoriesC.Scope Metal Detecting AccessoriesGarrett Metal Detecting AccessoriesGarrett Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsGarrett General AccessoriesTesoro/Laser AccessoriesViking Metal Detecting AccessoriesWhite's Metal Detecting AccessoriesWhite's Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsWhite's General AccessoriesXP Metal Detecting AccessoriesXP Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsXP General AccessoriesXP DEUS AccessoriesMakro Metal Detecting AccessoriesMAS Coils for Metal DetectorsNokta Metal Detecting AccessoriesMinelab Metal Detecting AccessoriesMinelab Coils, Coil Covers, Arm Cups, Stems & FittingsMinelab General AccessoriesMaz Metal Detecting AccessoriesPinpoint ProbesBarrelling and CleaningBatteries and ChargersCarry Bags for metal detectorsClothingFinds and Coin StorageGold PanningHeadphones for Metal DetectorsMagnets for Metal DetectingMagnifiersMiscellaneousFinds Pouches and ApronsTrowels and ScoopsDetectorPro Metal DetectingNEL Coils for Metal DetectorsNEL Coils for Garrett metal detectorsNEL Coils for Laser/Tesoro metal detectorsNEL Coils for Makro Metal DetectorsNEL Coils for Minelab metal detectorsNEL Coils for Whites metal detectorsNEL Coils for XP metal detectorsNEL Coils for Teknetics/Fisher/Discovery metal detectorsNEL COIL COVERSMetal Detecting Books & MapsArcheology BooksBadges and Buttons BooksBeach and Underwater Metal Detecting BooksBuckles BooksCleaning and Restoration BooksCeltic and Roman booksCoin and Token BooksCutlery BooksDress Accessory BooksFarming and Tools BooksGeneral Metal Detecting BooksGold Panning and Prospecting BooksHorse Furniture BooksIdentifying your finds BooksIron and Bronze Age BooksMapsMetal Detecting DVDsMedieval BooksPottery and BottlesResearch BooksSaxon and Viking BooksSealsShoebox LibrarySpecific Detector GuidesThimbles BooksWeights BooksGift Vouchers Security Metal Detectors Page
Information
About Regton Ltd
Contact Regton Team
Metal Detecting Code of Conduct & Environmental Information
New to metal detecting?
Personal Data Access (GDPR)
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Compare Products
You have no items to compare.
Community Poll
What is your favourite metal detector manufacturer ?
Personal Data Access (GDPR)
Sign Up for Our Newsletter:
Go!
© 2020 Regton Ltd. All Rights Reserved.
This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse this site you are agreeing to our use of cookies.
Find out more here.
x
